

SUMMURY

Innovative Web Developer with 4 years of experience in website design and coding. Demonstrated talent for front and back-end web development to optimize online presence. Seasoned expert in languages such as HTML, CSS, JavaScript, php, MySQL.

CONTACT

PHONE: +216 50 870 256

LINKEDIN: /maamoun-arissa

PORTFOLIO: https://maamoungrissa.me

E-MAIL: grissa.maamoun@gmail.com

SKILLS

HTML / CSS / JavaScript / PHP / MySql jQuery / AlpineJS / Tailwindcss VueJS / ReactJs / AngularJs NodeJs / ExpressJs / Redux MongoDb / Bootstrap / MaterialUi ReactNative / ionic-framework Laravel / Livewire Wordpress / opencart / joomla Foxpro / vb.net / c++

LANGUAGES

Arabic OOOO

English 0000

Russian 0000

MAAMOUN GRISSA

Web Developer

WORK EXPERIENCES

Frontend Web Developer Squadio, Riadh, Saudi Arabia. (Remote)

2021 - Today

Missions: Development & support of web applications...

Manager

Anytime & Anywhere, Sousse, Tunisia.

2021 - Current

Services: Development of static websites, e-commerce platforms, web and mobile applications, Graphic Design, Companies identity, Digital Marketing, SEO ...

Full Stack Web Developer Flegrei, Moscow, Russia

2019 - 2021

Development of websites, web and mobile applications:

- E-commerce plateforms using opencart cms.
- Catalog websites using Wordpress cms.
- Mobile app using lonic-framework & Angular Js + Api: Laravel 7.

Full Stack Web Developer Kvantum, Moscow, Russia (Remote)

2019 - 2021

Development of websites, web and mobile applications:

- Catalog websites using joomla cms.
- Development of web application using Laravel 7.

System Administrator Hotel LTI El Ksar. Sousse. Tunisia

2013 - 2018

Management and maintenance of computers equipment's, local networks, WIFI networks, telephony, surveillance cameras, ERP system and audiovisual Manager.

Software Developer

Tunisian Company of Equipment's, Tunis, Tunisia

2011 - 2012

Development of ERP system of the company using FoxPro.

EDUCATION

Higher institute of technological studies, Sousse, Tunisia

July 2011

Applied license in multimedia and web development

Higher institute of technological studies, Sousse, Tunisia

Cisco certificate: home & small business networking

